Diego Cattaneo

Frontend Developer Buenos Aires, Argentina

■ diegocattaneo@hotmail.com.ar

L +54 9 11 2251 8731

⊕ <u>dcattaneo.vercel.app</u>

github.com/dcattaneo

As a frontend developer with more than 2 years experience working with React and Typescript, and some backend skills using Node.js, I enjoy creating quality products to provide a good user experience, following best practices, which are essential for writing efficient, clean and reusable code.

Experience

Frontend Developer - Instituto Nacional de Tecnología Industrial (INTI)

Jan 2023 - Present

- I have worked with the team in the redesign and rebuild of the web application, as well as in its ongoing maintenance and improvement.
- · Collaborating on user experience improvements in order to increase their engagement.

Web Developer - Freelance

Mar 2021 - Dec 2022

- Custom websites based on clients needs using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and non-relational databases based on their needs.
- Communication channels, such as Slack or Zoom to keep clients informed about the progress of each project. This allowed for quick responses to questions and adjustments on the fly.

Investment Analyst- Instituto Nacional de Tecnología Industrial (INTI)

Mar 2013 - Dec 2022

- I have been in charge of investment analysis for the Operational Sub-management of Construction and Infrastructure.
- Drafting of specific agreements with other organizations and management of the administrative process.
- Delivered training courses on procurement procedures to various departments of the organization.

Education

Degree in Computer Science - UBA

Jan 2018 - Present

Bachelor's Degree in International Trade - UNLAM

Jul 2009 - Jan 2017

Languages

Spanish

English

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Node
- Express
- React
- React Query
- Next

- Typescript
- Git
- CSS-in-JS
- Tailwind CSS
- APIRest
- Mongo
- MySQL
- Zustand